{
    "questionanswers": {
        "questionanswer": [
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+4?",
                "option": [
                    45,
                    44,
                    46,
                    47
                ],
                "ans": 44
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+5?",
                "option": [
                    45,
                    49,
                    46,
                    47
                ],
                "ans": 45
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+6?",
                "option": [
                    45,
                    44,
                    46,
                    48
                ],
                "ans": 46
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+7?",
                "option": [
                    51,
                    44,
                    50,
                    47
                ],
                "ans": 47
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+8?",
                "option": [
                    48,
                    50,
                    51,
                    52
                ],
                "ans": 48
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+9?",
                "option": [
                    50,
                    49,
                    51,
                    45
                ],
                "ans": 49
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+10?",
                "option": [
                    52,
                    54,
                    50,
                    48
                ],
                "ans": 50
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+11?",
                "option": [
                    54,
                    51,
                    55,
                    48
                ],
                "ans": 51
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+12?",
                "option": [
                    50,
                    51,
                    52,
                    49
                ],
                "ans": 52
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+13?",
                "option": [
                    53,
                    49,
                    50,
                    52
                ],
                "ans": 53
            },
            {
                "question": "Total of 5*8+14?",
                "option": [
                    53,
                    54,
                    50,
                    52
                ],
                "ans": 54
            }
        ]
    }
}